JASON CRABTREE

Digital Designer living in Auckland, NZ

https://jasontcrabtree.com https://lodestone.studio jasontcrabtree@gmail.com

Phone: 027-322-4961

RÉSUMÉ OBJECTIVE

I shine when working on thoughtful experiences and in teamwork, systems-thinking and problem-solving. In my work, I strive to bring people together to work towards long-term outcomes. I have a strong set of generalist skills from past roles and a passion for learning. I'm excited to join your team and contribute to your digital and service design challenges.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Psychology completed *Feb 2009–July 2012* Massey University, New Zealand.

SKILLS and CAPABILITIES

- Service Design and Journey Mapping
- User experience design (UX)
- User interface design (UI)
- User and Customer research (Qualitative and quantitative)
- Workshop facilitation and planning
- Design Sprints and Design Process
- Communication and collaboration
- Problem-solving and critical-analysis
- HTML, CSS and JS development.

TOOLS

Figma, Sketch, HTML, CSS, macOS, Windows, Adobe, Agile.

ACHIEVEMENTS and AWARDS

- FreeCodeCamp Responsive Web Design Certificate (2019).
- Customer-First Award, IAG NZ (2017) for interal customer advocacy.
- Received consistent internal IAG awards for teamwork, leadership, collaboration and innovation.
- Community Toastmasters Club for 15–Mo. Session leader and facilitator.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Freelance Web Designer & Developer via Lodestone Studio, NZ, Oct 2020–Current.

Travelling, Job Hunting, Online Education Dublin & London, Feb 2019–Aug 2020.

INSURANCE AUSTRALIA GROUP, New Zealand Oct 2014–Jan 2019

- Customer Experience Design Lead 11 months

 Designed improved digital, phone and
 in-person UX and CX experiences. Key projects
 of customer journey mapping, service-design,
 personas and workshop facilitation.
- Customer Insights Consultant 1 year
 User Research role focused on phone based
 qualitative interviews with customers, NPS
 reporting, insights, analysis and presentations.
- Senior Insurance Claims Manager 8 months Managed a portfolio of ~50 ongoing complex claims plus mentoring and coaching. Built SharePoint tools to improve team efficiency.
- Insurance Claims Manager 2 years

 Customer relationship role managing a portfolio of 200 domestic claims.

ST JOHN AMBULANCE, New Zealand Sept 2012-Aug 2014

• Emergency Medical Call Handler 2 years
Phone-based medical triage and emergency
ambulance dispatch in life-or-death situations.